criticker.com 2019-05-16

# Criticker - Privacy Policy

Criticker.com uses cookies to recognize visitors and provide a better experience. Learn more about how we use cookies [in our privacy policy](https://www.criticker.com/privacy/). By continuing to use the site, or by pressing agree, you are giving your consent to our use of cookies.  

## Information Gathering

On registration, Criticker asks for your email address, name, age and gender. Your email address is the only field which is required information, because it is necessary in case your password is lost.

## Information Sharing

Criticker.com will not share your email address or any personal information with any third party. We will not make your email address visible to other users.

## Emails from Criticker

If you choose not to receive emails from Criticker about recommendations and new features, you will not receive any. Criticker may still send you emails when legally required to do so -- such as when there is a change to this privacy policy or information regarding your account.

## Cookies

Criticker.com may set and update cookies on your computer, which allow us to remember your username and preferences which you set. Criticker will not set cookies with the intent of marketing.

Criticker.com uses a tool which collects requests for pages and passes elements of them to search engines to assist them in indexing this site. We control the configuration of the tool and are responsible for any information sent to the search engines.

## Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Changes to this Policy

Criticker may update this policy. We will notify you about any significant changes by email.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please send an email to [info@criticker.com](mailto:info@criticker.com). We will answer your question as soon as possible.
